On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back of
my super strong partner, Lammis!
The name's Boxxo! Hello there!
That means yes, by the way!
Leave him to me.
Has Heavy always had
such superhuman strength?
I knew he had blessing
of might like Lamas,
but I guess he's been
holding back this whole time.
Seems like a lie by omission and he
claims not to believe in telling lies.
What are you?
Some kind of monster?
Sir, a clergyman going
around murdering people.
I am a human being first
and a clergyman second.
Please, I'm sorry.
I'll quit my bandit ways.
I beg you, sir, just spare my life.
The gods say that death is serene.
It comes to each of us impartially, but
there is one point on which I beg to differ.
Death itself may very well
be impartial. Have mercy!
I'll pay whatever you ask!
Those who meet out death must not be
impartial where scumbags are concerned.
DO YOU WANT WOMEN OR RINCES?
PLEASE!
DON'T KILL ME. PLEASE. DON'T KILL ME.
ENOUGH.
DON'T THINK YOU CAN MAKE A FOOL OF ME.
YOU WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS!
YOU IDIOTS ARE FINISHED, YOU HEAR ME!
The Stratum Lord.
It has to be.
The ogre that dwells on the
top floor of the desert pillar?
That is the Stratum Lord. You're all dead.
Say goodbye and meet your end.
Awake, dual ogre!
Is it meal time?
I love meal time.
And the eating is good today, my monster.
Stop! Don't eat me!
That one is my prey
and I shan't yield him.
Hey you you can't steal from us!
I could say the same thing to you.
I staked my claim on him first, after all.
Current time, let's go.
I'll deal with him.
Please be careful.
I promised you I'd help and I will.
Please know how I appreciate it.
Let's hurry up.
We can take down this monster.
I know it.
Master Boxo and the rest of
us will make quick work of it.
Meat meat everywhere.
What can we make a meal of them?
Save the thighs and entrails for me now.
Time for this stratum's final showdown.
Take that!
Better not underestimate
us! What? No! Wait a minute!
Uh-oh! Barrier time!
Points decreased by 2,222.
I only lost a thousand points when that
monstrous eight-legged crocodile rammed me!
You won't smash us! Dumb human!
What's going on?
Why didn't that take down the monster?
If those attacks keep hitting me,
I'll be scrap metal in no time.
This foe is beyond any of us.
We must run.
Not a good plan.
Come to think of it, this is the first
time we've fought a Stratum Lord head-on.
Until now, we've exploited
their weak points.
And being under the Nether
Lord's command might
have made the other
ones weaker than usual.
Change!
Quick, this way!
Come on, go!
Our feet is getting away!
As if that would make anyone stop running!
It sure is sounding real loud
and scary back there, Bobso!
You could even win a reward!
Damn!
What should I do?
Think! Water? Ice? Flames?
So much food!
Meat made everywhere!
What?
It's eating the monsters!
Oh, I get it.
They're really hungry.
Their stomachs must outweigh their anger.
In that case, I'll give them my
personal fave, authentic barbecue sauce.
What's that?
It smells so yummy.
It is so yummy.
That's the real deal stuff for you.
This should buy us a little time.
I am sorry.
I should have told you all more about
the Stratum Lord before we went in there.
What are we supposed to do
against an opponent like that?
Normally, I'd respond with
a carefree, hello there.
But I don't know either.
Instead of being useful,
I was just a burden.
I'm sorry, Master Boxo.
And I allowed my anger
to get the better of me.
I apologize for exposing
everyone to grave danger.
Boxo's right.
Apologizing will not
improve the situation.
Instead, let us think on
what to do about that ogre.
At least our choices are clear.
We can either run away or defeat it.
It's too strong of an opponent.
I think we should consider running.
But we left Tashtay in there.
He could get away.
Chances are he's already dead,
or more likely that the dual ogre
will eat him in a matter of minutes.
Not even that magic skull ring could
bring the foul monster to bear.
Well, to be fair, the skull ring
can only handle simple commands.
When it comes to a Stratum Lord,
signaling it to attack is
the most one could hope for.
So speaking of Tashtay's skull
ring, if the dual ogre ate it,
there's no chance the ogre would
then gain control of it, right?
Oh, Lamas, that's not...
not outside the realm of possibility.
And if it were to come to pass,
the Stratum Lord would suddenly be
in control of a slew of monsters.
What if it uses those monsters
to attack the village?
It appears we've narrowed
down our options.
We should take it down once and for all.
But I'll defer to you, Master Boxo.
I would appreciate it if a decision
like that were not up to me, Michele.
Um, guys, did you forget
that I'm a vending machine?
What exactly are you hoping for from me?
No, I can't think like that.
Okay, er, uh, Bill, it is...
Need more information?
You've got it.
It has two heads.
The right is male, the left, female.
They seem to disagree on things
sometimes, but they basically get along.
Its body is much tougher than
steel, and you've seen its power.
It probably tops even Lamas
in terms of its raw strength.
My attacks are formidable, no doubt.
But aren't Lamas' and
Mishuel's even more so?
I thought they could penetrate
something as strong as steel.
We need to determine the
dual ogre's blessings, too.
Blessing of might, yeah?
Seems obvious.
Yeah, that power was off the charts.
And the problematic one is hardening.
That makes it way tougher all around.
Yeah, that would partly explain
why my attack didn't work.
So blessing of might and hardening.
Sounds simple, but it is hard to beat.
We maybe could have worked something
out if the captain were here with us.
Yes, the blessing of eye breach.
There's no use in wishing
for what we don't have.
We'll just have to work
with what we've got.
Wise words.
Now what do we have?
We know it's a big
eater and heavy drinker.
Huh, that sounds a lot
like Japanese ogres.
There are old tales about attacking
them after you get them drunk.
Drunk? Alcohol!
I can offer it limitless alcohol! Okay!
Is this?
Oh, it's booze.
And there's quite a lot of it.
Do we get that thing to drink all this?
Yeah, but how?
Good question.
Maybe they'll drink it if a
pretty girl pours it for them.
What do we know about an ogre's
concept of beauty, though?
Uh-huh. Good point.
Well, we could find a pretty ogre lady.
Do you know any of those?
Ooh!
Maybe we could make it
hallucinate a hot ogre lady.
I've had a fair number of
encounters with ogres in my time,
so it's not out of the question.
I don't know how to speak
their language, unfortunately.
I know of it, and I can teach you
a smattering at the very least.
Don't know if it'll work or not,
but we're all out of other ideas.
Hello there!
Hm. Boxo.
Here he is, folks, a rock ogre monster.
But it's actually heavy with
an illusion cast on him.
And here I am on his back, transformed
into a vending machine made for kids.
32-liter plastic bottles.
All the water inside's been replaced
with various alcoholic drinks.
Well, here goes nothing, Boxo.
If you decide it's too dangerous,
don't hesitate to retreat.
Please be careful.
Who are you?
What's a rock ogre doing in our lair?
That's ogre speak we learned from Hulemy.
It's a greeting of sorts.
What is that? Water?
Now let's get rid of the strings and caps.
I know this scent.
Who's my favorite?
Oh, it's true.
They do like to drink.
But it wouldn't hurt to slow down.
Give me this one, too.
That's good.
I've never had a drink that
tastes like this before.
I was just feeling thirsty, too.
What a thoughtful rock ogre.
Is there enough?
But those last two
bottles are the strongest.
Hopefully they'll do the trick.
The booze is making me feel
nice and sleepy. Let's rest.
Let it be a waste. Let's drink.
Whoa, it worked.
I don't think a drunk ogre is
going to wake up that easily.
What are we doing with that?
It's filled with booze.
Check it.
Okay, the needle went in.
It appears they have to be conscious
to use the blessing of hardening.
This syringe was supposed to be for
taking out the elder tree fiend,
but it sure came in handy anyway.
I do feel kind of bad for attacking
this thing while it's asleep.
It pains me as well, but in my mind,
there's no room for pity when
you're fighting a duel to the death.
Do you agree, Master Boxo? Yes.
Well, I suppose I'll take this side.
Think you can handle that side, Mishuo?
All right.
Yeah? What is it, Boxxo?
Huh?
You said beat them with you?
Oh, I get it.
If you're the one who defeats the enemy,
then you'll gain the winning points.
Oh, I understand. Let's see then.
If I swing Boxxo and I hit them...
Hold on, Lamas.
Let's attack at the same time.
All right!
One, two, three!
That's a slap!
Stratum lord for you even though i split
it three ways with llamas and Mishel
i still got over a million points is
it all right if i absorb the dual ogre
hold on just one more moment there's a
valuable part in here but i'm cool with
you doing it after i retrieve that go
ahead kiko you much That's appreciated,
Hulemy.
Hmm?
We'd better do a quick recon
to see what became of Tash-Tay.
Indeed, I would be most grateful.
Did it just get cold in here? Sure did.
Is it coming from above?
This is rather strange.
It's much colder in
here than it is outside.
It's not the night chill creeping in.
Whatever do you think this
could mean, Master Boxo?
Why are you asking me?
Sheesh, it is freezing!
Yeah, it literally is, and like how
with us being in the middle of a desert?
I know this feeling.
This sensation.
Could it be?
Huh?
He's been frozen in ice?
Everyone, please gather
around Boxxo, quickly!
Now, Boxxo, raise your barrier! Good call.
Activate barrier!
Snowing?
Here in the scorching sand stratum?
That's bizarre.
I don't know of any monster on this
stratum that can control air temperature.
so you are a snow fairy you are surely
mistaken if you regard us as enemies.
we're friendly we simply
came here to see that man.
what was that for we
snow fairies are not a
race that has ever been
known to kill people.
so wantedly as that
what's a snow child doing
with humans in the first
place these people are.
my friends humans are scum
you know that too don't
you it's true that i live
my whole life on the run.
from humans director bear
told me before about the
mysterious power snow
children like kiko you have.
legend has it that if you
behead a snow child on
the day it becomes an
adult they will transform
into a magical ice statue
that will never melt
as for the severed head
it will continue to utter.
There are curses that have the power to
contaminate entire
regions in one fell swoop.
Not all humans are bad!
There are some you can trust!
And not just humans!
Feel this trustworthy!
There are many people like them!
You poor thing.
The humans have tricked you.
How pathetic.
No, they haven't!
You misunderstand!
We are not your enemies!
Not my enemies. That's right!
So then, you also work
for the Netherlord? What?
The Netherlord?
Well, uh...
No, seems not.
Now that I look closely at that steel box,
it looks just like that magic item
Boxxo of which the Netherlord spoke.
How about that?
I'm famous and didn't even know it.
Am I to take these statements to
mean you work for the Netherlord?
Yes, I am his medicine
general known as Sulream.
The Netherlord's general?
The Netherlord saved me just
before some humans who had
captured me were about to
murder me quite ruthlessly.
I have been by his side ever since.
That's so well timed it bugs
me what if the Nether Lord
set that up so he could get
his hands on a snow fairy's
powers sounds like something
he'd try my lord's words and
his commands mean everything
to me you're in our way goodbye
we're in big trouble the second we step
through this barrier we'll freeze well Well,
I have plenty of points, so I
could try to tough this out.
Does every snow fairy have
incredible powers like she does?
So crazy.
Our power levels vary, but it is
unusual to see someone on such a level.
She is rather powerful.
How long do you think
this blizzard will last?
Well, with this kind of power, the
storm could go on for two to three days.
That'd be bad.
Foxo, how long can your barrier hold?
Let's see if I'm using up ten points
a second based on my current points.
I'll try again to persuade her. But how?
I'll be fine even if I
have to step outside.
Really?
I am moved and grateful for your concern.
But still, I want to stop
her, even if I get hurt.
She is me, or who I'd be
if I had never met Field.
Had I also met the
Netherlord before Field,
I'm sure I'd have turned out
like her, I'm sorry to say.
You feel sorry for her?
I would be lying if I said I did not.
But there is more to it.
Please trust me.
Okay, I'll trust in that. Still...
Boxxo, do you know what time it is?
Um, it'll be midnight
in less than a minute.
Great!
Then I will be back.
Say what?
Those two are strangely calm.
Do they know something?
Hold on.
Did snow just start blowing
in from the other way, too?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it did.
It's pushing back.
Wait, who could that be?
Another snow fairy?
Why do you think she showed up?
Do you think she came to save us?
I don't know her intentions,
but I do know her boots are
exactly the same as Kikuyu's.
Master Boxxo,
though it's increased far beyond what
I have always felt from her till now,
I do sense the same energy as Kikuyu's.
What do you suppose this could mean?
That means she's Kikuyu, obviously.
I get it.
She grew up in the blink of an eye.
Wait, what?
Is that actually Kikuyu?
Huh? There's no way!
I heard that the moment Snow
Fairies reached their 18th birthday,
they suddenly grow up
into full-fledged adults.
Could this be that?
Which means, today's
Kikuyu's 18th birthday?
Of course!
That's why she's been keeping such a close
eye on her calendar the past few days.
Today's the day with the
red circle around it.
And now it's just past midnight!
Her magical powers are far
beyond what they were before.
I didn't know the change
would be so dramatic.
They even rival that general's powers,
which is really saying something!
It's an equal match.
No, Kikuyu is pushing back!
I'll ask one last time.
Will you leave this place?
There is something that
I still need to do.
I can't afford to die now.
I have my own mission as well.
Fine, you win. I'll leave.
Alright, my friends.
It's still a little cold,
but it's safe to come out.
My goodness, you really are, Kikuyu, then.
Yes, it's still me.
I really wish I could have seen her
in the moment of transformation.
I wonder if it's like a transformation
sequence in a magical girl anime.
I'd love to have recorded it.
Foxo, are you having weird thoughts again?
You could even win a reward.
There you go, trying
to play innocent. Well,
I guess with all that settled,
we can say things are wrapped
up on this stratum, too.
I feel for heavy, though.
Are you okay to leave? Yes.
Tosh take out even more than he
had coming to him, by my math.
Besides, watching him suffer was
never going to fully erase my grief.
That will be with me till the
end of my days, or so I believe.
Therefore, I am satisfied.
Huh, I didn't know Heavy could
make such an inspiring face.
Seems like you're gonna be okay.
Am I to take your statement to mean
that you were concerned about me?
How sweet.
My only concern is whether you're
trying to sniff my boots or not.
But at the same time, boots
don't matter anymore, I guess.
It's really too bad.
If you were still feeling down,
I would have been willing to give
you my boots to cheer you up.
Apologies, but were you
being sincere just now?
Huh?
You don't care about boots anymore, right?
It's true that I was driven by
revenge to search for footwear,
but it's also true that I
have awoken to its appeal.
Now, please make good on your
offer and take off those boots.
I have no interest in you personally,
but I've had my eye on your
boots for quite some time.
You're indifferent about your clothing?
So I suspect those boots
you've been wearing.
will give off the most
exquisite fragrance.
Die, you nasty pervert!
I take back what I said!
I want a play too, guys!
Lammis, that's too big!
I can produce any amount of snow you like.
That's about when a
snowball fight broke out.
Shall we take part in the snow
battle as well, Master Boxo?
You bet.
The snowball fight on the scorching
sand stratum sounds sweet.
Hello there.
so
I'll come back back to the back
of my life I'll come back to the
end of my
life
handle them on my
own you could even
win a reward you